{"questions" : {
        "0" : {
            "question" : "",
            "A" : "",
            "B" : "",
            "C" : "",
            "right" : ""},
        "1" : {
            "question" : "Where _______ from? I’m from Russia.",
            "A" : "you are",
            "B" : "you",
            "C" : "are you",
            "right" : "are you"},
        "2" : {
            "question" : "We have ___ house in Moscow.",
            "A" : "any",
            "B" : "a",
            "C" : "an",
            "right" : "a"},
        "3" : {
            "question" : "I have two _______, a boy and a girl.",
            "A" : "sons",
            "B" : "daughters",
            "C" : "children",
            "right" : "children"},
        "4" : {
            "question" : "I work in a _______. I’m a doctor.",
            "A" : "hospital",
            "B" : "hotel",
            "C" : "supermarket",
            "right" : "hospital"},
        "5" : {
            "question" : "This is my brother. _______ name’s Paul.",
            "A" : "Her",
            "B" : "His",
            "C" : "He’s",
            "right" : "His"},
        "6" : {
            "question" : "_______ five people in my family.",
            "A" : "They are",
            "B" : "There is",
            "C" : "There are",
            "right" : "There are"},
        "7" : {
            "question" : "I get up _______ 7 o’clock in the morning.",
            "A" : "for",
            "B" : "at",
            "C" : "in",
            "right" : "at"},
        "8" : {
            "question" : "I like apples, but I _______ bananas.",
            "A" : "don’t like",
            "B" : "like",
            "C" : "do like",
            "right" : "don’t like"},
        "9" : {
            "question" : "Excuse me, _______ speak French?",
            "A" : "do you",
            "B" : "you do",
            "C" : "you",
            "right" : "do you"},
        "10" : {
            "question" : "How much are _______ shoes?",
            "A" : "this",
            "B" : "these",
            "C" : "that",
            "right" : "these"}}}
